SPOOKY IN LOVE
I now unveil here for you, the heartwarming love letter of Hwagyeongdang,
Who was a great poet and painter of her era.
If this was found in the process of relocating Kang Pyeong-gun's tomb,
Would that then mean this love letter was in his coffin as well?
Yes. How heart-wrenching.
It's romantic, don't you think so?
Are long-term cold cases really your specialty?
Yeah.
How would you like another?
One that's been cold for over 300 years.
Me and you.
EPISODE 6
A couple of ground rules before we start working together.
Rule number one: We share everything,
And we never go to a scene alone.
Rule number two:
We keep a safe distance when we're on the move.
Rule number three:
We always leave at least one seat between us when we sit down.
So, let me see if I got everything.
A male ghost appeared during an event
Unveiling a 300-year-old love letter that was found
While workers relocated an ancient grave.
Three hundred? My goodness.
You weren't lying. That was a really long time ago.
So what can you tell me about the ghost who appeared in front of you?
He's an artist, actually.
The one who painted Hwagyeongdang's portrait at Yeeon.
Well, I guess all we need to do is find his remains, right?
Not really. He's not the one we should go after.
We should look for Hwagyeongdang.
Wait, he wrote the letter, right?
I don't get it.
What's the point of looking for someone else's remains?
The thing is
What Dowon told me was a whole different story than the one we heard.
Apparently, Kang Pyeong-gun, who was of royal blood,
Started pursuing Hwagyeong, even though she was Dowon's lover.
-What have you found? -He's a painter named Dowon.
He and Hwagyeong grew up together.
His name means nothing. I care not what it is.
All that matters is my Hwagyeong.
She's mine.
And I must come up with a plan
To ensnare him and draw Hwagyeong to my side.
I told you to come down a thousand times!
You wretched woman, why do you refuse to listen?
Do you intend to mock me to the very end? Damn you! You insolent--
Who are you? Wait!
Good heavens! This man This man is attacking a nobleman!
-How dare he! A nobleman! -He's attacking a nobleman!
-Help me, please! He tried to kill me! -Please! Wait! Please don't hurt him!
Assaulting a nobleman.
With the right connections at the police bureau,
They can turn it into a crime against the social order,
One punishable by death.
Let him go.
Don't do this to him, I'm begging you! Stop it, please!
Stop! Please, stop!
Halt!
Kang Pyeong-gun's obsession turned into madness.
He held Dowon's life over her head until she had no choice but to marry him.
Where are you bound in such a hurry?
How dare you.
You tried to deceive me, and you will answer for it.
No! Wait!
Hwagyeong attempted to escape Kang Pyeong-gun's tyranny,
But she was brutally murdered
-before Dowon's eyes. -No!
Forgive me, dear.
Kang Pyeong-gun went so far as to hide Hwagyeong's death.
After taking an empty palanquin to Mount Geumgangsan,
He spread the ridiculous rumor
That Hwagyeongdang had disappeared into the mountains.
To this day, no one knows where she was actually buried.
Hold on a second. Do you think Dowon could have been lying to you?
The way I see it,
When it comes to romantic relationships, you have to hear both sides of the story.
Besides, Hwagyeongdang's love letter was found in Kang Pyeong-gun's tomb, so
He said there's evidence that could prove that wrong.
Can you look into that? That's in the "living department."
So it's right up your alley.
By the way, I was doing some research
And it turns out Dowon didn't get recognition during his lifetime,
But he was later recognized as an important artist thanks to Hwajeopdo.
This place is kinda
I don't know,
I think this feels more like Cheon Yeo-ri's department, actually.
Oh, wow.
What if Dowon was wrong?
Oh!
Hello, sir.
What's with the sickle?
So, what did you say you were looking for?
Yes, I'm here because I heard there's a relic
Of the painter Dowon that was passed down through this family.
-Yeah. -Hmm.
Excuse me, sir. May I take a look at this too?
Hmm?
So it turns out the two love letters were actually just one.
That's right. And she didn't write it for Kang Pyeong-gun either.
She wrote it for Dowon.
I thought this was the Joseon-era version of Ghost,
But this guy is just a psychopath.
A fake empty palanquin? That was the best he could do? So much for royal blood.
You know what? I think that's why.
It's because he was royalty.
He couldn't stand the fact that her heart wasn't his.
I want to find Hwagyeongdang
And reunite her with Dowon once and for all.
This whole thing has been keeping her bound to Kang Pyeong-gun for far too long.
We have to figure this out.
Don't be like that, please.
You're not going to walk away now, are you?
We're in too deep already. Even if I wanted to back out, I couldn't.
The thing is, the prosecution caught wind of what happened last time, you know?
And we struggled to keep it under wraps.
So I've been thinking, at least until things settle down--
-Mrs. Ok-- -Anyway, that Ju Sin-ho painting
You gave me last time really helped
Excuse me. It's Cheon Yeo-ri.
What does she want?
Hello, Ms. Cheon.
We're talking a lot lately, aren't we, huh?
Ah! Of course. Okay, sure. See you tomorrow.
You don't think Cheon Yeo-ri could've caught on to something, do you?
No, no way.
Well, I'll find out when I meet with her, I guess.
Yes, so in other news, I'm meeting with Yeeon's director tomorrow.
I'm going to see if anything else comes up.
Hmm. Okay, no worries. I'll join you after work.
Hmm? I can go there by myself, you know.
Uh, you can't do that.
Remember rule number one?
We have to share everything we learn,
And we can't go to a scene alone, that's what we agreed on.
And besides, we have a team dinner afterward.
Team dinner?
Yeah. We've earned it after all this hard work.
That pork rind place again?
Ah. That sounds pretty good. To be safe, I'll bring an extra shirt.
Well, by the way, um,
I wanted to do a little more digging before asking, um Mmm
Where did the artwork on display in the Reina Hotel come from?
Oh, the artwork. Um, our art team handles all of that.
We usually get them through Gallery Cheon, which my aunt runs.
Why?
Is there a problem, or
Oh, no, no. Don't worry about it.
It's not that there's anything wrong with Reina or Gallery Cheon.
It's just that Reina's name came up during an art distribution investigation.
ACQUISITIONS AND TRANSACTION RECORD
OF ARTWORK PLACED IN HOTELS
Are these all the art pieces Reina has on display right now?
Yes.
I sent each of the transfer files separately to your email.
Great, so what I need now
Is a list with all the artwork Reina has purchased
Through Gallery Cheon over the past ten years.
Check all the market values against what we paid.
Bring that over to me once you're done, Mr. Bong.
And don't tell anyone. No one can know.
Got it.
I'm busy, what do you want?
Have a seat.
What is it?
So about the Reina Hotel case you mentioned, how's that going?
-Again with this artwork stuff? -I'm just curious, don't be like that.
Whatever. What exactly do you wanna know?
You said someone started digging and got shut down. Who was it?
Whatever, no point in hiding anything from you anyway.
So originally, Nam Ji-hun from Unit Three was looking into it.
Then the higher-ups told him to shut it down.
Now I'm doing it.
If the money's gone, that's probably laundering.
But since the artwork disappeared, bribery's more like it, isn't it?
Well, yeah, that's what I've been thinking too.
But why would the Chief Prosecutor do the dirty work himself? I don't get it.
Exactly.
I also thought that was weird. That's why I'm looking into it.
There's a lot I don't know,
But at least I know where the money went now.
Reina, right?
You're acting weird.
You're obsessed with Reina.
You're up to something, aren't you?
I'm not up to anything. What do you mean?
I'm completely swamped just dealing with my cold cases.
Well, okay. So it's not Reina? Is that it?
It's not Reina.
I'm going there later. Wanna come with me?
I can't. I have somewhere to be. Great work, by the way.
Hey.
Well, that's surprising.
You're more of a romantic than I thought, Ms. Cheon.
Of course it's interesting to me, I mean, they're my ancestors.
But why are you so emotionally invested in a love letter from that long ago?
You're right, I know.
It's not the romance. There's more to it than that.
It felt like the words of someone who was anticipating something, you know?
A final farewell.
I don't know why, but it really stuck with me.
I wonder where Hwagyeongdang was buried. I'm really curious.
I just don't get it.
Why would someone with as much on your plate as you, Ms. Cheon,
Be so curious about something like that?
Well, if there's anything you'd like to know that isn't in the public records,
You might want to check out the alma mater of my late father, the founding chairman.
All the records related to Kang Pyeong-gun were donated
To the Yeeon Museum, so they're all in one place.
We're planning to donate the letter too, once it's officially unveiled.
Yes?
-Oh, Mr. Kang. -Hi, sorry I'm late.
-Just made it back from the airport. -Oh, not at all.
You made it just in time. Have a seat.
We were just catching up over the phone.
That's right. She told me you were coming, so I insisted on joining.
The trip here must've been so tiring.
-Not at all. -Oh, my goodness.
Gang-uk?
-Um, what? -"Um, what"?
Hey, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
You and Ms. Lee seem pretty close.
Oh, she's close with my mother.
Anyway, talk about good timing. I almost missed you there.
Where are you coming in from?
They found some artifacts at the Baekhyeon Leisure Town site
So they had to stop construction.
-Hmm. -I went there to sort things out.
-Hmm. -Oh.
For you.
W-What's this?
I was on a business trip in Europe and I thought they'd suit you.
Thank you. No one's given me gloves before.
They're lovely.
Mm-hmm.
You're not here because of what I said, are you?
What do you mean?
Ah, this is where the money went, isn't it?
I get it now. That's why you're here so often.
I know something's up. What is it? Just say it.
-Spit it out, come on. What? -Ah, it's nothing. Nothing's going on.
-Hey, wait for me! -Hey, don't do that.
Oh, come on.
-Just for a minute. -Get off me.
-So we meet again. -So we do.
Oh. I know you. You're the famous Cheon Yeo-ri, right?
Nice to meet you. Uh
I'm Prosecutor Im Seo-hyeon. Prosecutor Ma and I work at the same district office.
I saw the article about you two, by the way.
Uh, congratulations.
So when's the, um, engagement ceremony?
Oh. That would've been amazing.
But they just published a follow-up article.
-Sadly, they were just rumors. -Oh, really?
Huh. Uh
We're going to grab some dinner. Why don't you join us?
When did I say yes to that?
Oh, come on. You always have dinner by yourself anyway.
Let's call it a team dinner so it's an excuse to eat together.
Right? Let's go together.
Come on, just forget it. Uh, let's just let' s get out of here.
That sounds good.
Let's go. Together.
The four of us.
Look at this.
Check this out. We took this the last time we came here.
Whoa. You two have the couple selfie thing down.
That's That's not a couple selfie.
Im insisted we take a picture since we were here, so I just went along with it--
Well, you look good together.
Thank you.
All right, let's have a toast then. Our beers are here.
-Sure. -Cheers!
Oh, come on
Ah. I feel like you had to tone down the meal because of us, so I
I feel bad.
You know, since we work for the government,
We have no choice but to follow public service rules
So we have to pay separately.
The pasta here is really good.
And the ramen too, it's good.
-You eat ramen often? -Mm-hmm.
Sometimes I do. It's a good quick meal, very convenient.
Oh, really? I always thought people from chaebol families
Only ate specially prepared meals,
Fancy fine dining, 12-course feasts and all that kinda stuff.
So, if you like ramen, we should have it by the Hangang River.
It tastes even better when you're by the riverbank.
I can't wait to go there and have some ramen with you two.
Can you just just, you know just
What'd I say?
What about you, Prosecutor Ma?
Have you ever had ramen by the Hangang River?
-Yeah, well-- -Oh, he lives for it.
Back when we worked at the Southern District,
We ran into each other while jogging the day after a team dinner,
Got ramen for our hangovers, and went to the office together.
I didn't know people ate ramen for hangovers.
I'll have to try that out, you know, at some point.
That's nice.
Just let me know when, I wanna try it too.
What?
Of course. Let's do it. It's a plan.
Ramen by the river, the four us.
There. Have some.
-My goodness. -Eat it, come on.
Go ahead.
Oh
-You did that for me, Gang-uk? -No, just eat.
Are you okay with beer? You don't like it that much.
I drink beer sometimes.
You really surprised me there.
You're a lot more thoughtful than I thought you'd be, Prosecutor Ma.
Judging by the way you treat Prosecutor Im,
It's safe to say you're pretty caring.
Well, if I'm being honest, he surprised me too.
I didn't know Gang-uk had a sweet side.
I wasn't being thoughtful.
I was just worried she'd spill the food all over herself.
-She's really clumsy, actually-- -Exactly, and that was thoughtful.
You love me.
What? No, I don't. Waiter?
Can we get another round here, please?
Oh. You're the designated driver, right?
-Yes, hi. -There you go, thanks.
-Sure. -Where'd you park? I can give you a ride.
It's fine. I'll go get my car in the morning.
I'll take a cab.
-You sure? -Mm-hmm. Later.
-All right, see you tomorrow. -Bye.
Well, next time, we'll meet up by the river for ramen.
Thanks again, sir.
-I'll give you a ride. -Oh. It's all right.
Uh, I think I'll just I'll just walk home.
To get some fresh air.
Can I walk you there?
That's okay.
-Get home safe. -Mm-hmm.
Oh, no. That's not the right department. Don't send that to them. Yeah.
Oh, I'll I'll call you back tomorrow, okay? Bye.
Yeo-ri, what did Ms. Lee say? Any developments or anything?
-No developments. -Oh.
By the way, that was a close call, right? I did good, didn't I?
Yeah, that was really nice of you.
Im sure loved it.
I didn't do it for Im, you know.
I was just looking out for you, Yeo-ri. Don't you get it?
That doesn't make any sense, does it?
Im Seo-hyeon is the one who would be affected if we touched.
And Min-hwan was right, you were thoughtful and sweet.
Sweet? Don't say that, Yeo-ri.
You know that's not fair, come on. If I'm being honest here,
I was so busy watching Min-hwan being sly, and trying to manage Seo-hyeon,
I couldn't even tell if the pasta was going through my mouth or my nose.
Wait, Yeo-ri.
-Are you a little bit-- -Of course I'm not.
Ah, I didn't finish. How do you know what I was gonna say?
Whatever you say, my answer won't change.
Did my hands touch you?
Um, I'm not sure. But I don't think so.
Uh, since your accident,
Have you ever done something like this?
This is my first time.
Uh, and I think, as far as I know,
Only my hands trigger the effect.
Good. I think we're fine, then.
And if not, I'm totally okay with it.
Uh, please just don't worry about it.
So, for now
Uh, let's just keep an eye on you.
If you don't see anything by tomorrow,
Then I guess you should be in the clear.
You really don't have to worry, Yeo-ri.
It's fine. We'll just handle things as they come.
Still, if you see something, give me a call.
Okay.
He won't see them. He won't see them.
Of course he won't see them.
He's not calling, but he shouldn't be calling anyway.
He's not gonna see them.
He's not--
Do you see a ghost?
No. I don't see them. I'm calling to let you know.
Oh my gosh, you scared me. I thought you saw a ghost.
I said call me if you see anything, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't meet him.
-Come out. Show yourself! Who's there? -choice. I have to do it for the clan.
Come on, there's gotta be something else we can do.
Wait. I just thought of something!
Yep, hello?
How about now?
I'm a little worried.
Oh. Pretty sure I don't see anything.
At least not yet. I'm gonna call you if I do.
-Gang-uk -Yes?
This isn't gonna work.
I'll just handle this case on my own, like I always do.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Uh, I don't see them,
But even if I do, it's not like it's my first time experiencing this.
I'm used to it by now.
I have my own ways of dealing with them now.
I'm not on your level, but I'm not that bad.
Even so
And the truth is, I'm curious too.
This centuries-old mystery has really drawn me in.
I have to see how it ends.
Okay, sounds good.
But you have to call me the second anything happens, got it?
Okay.
Sleep well.
No sign of them. No need to worry.
PROSECUTOR MA
Great, I'm glad.
Come in.
You wanted to see me?
Here, let's have a cup of tea.
You're more of a coffee person, though, aren't you?
Hmm. Well, um, I'm staying away from caffeine for now.
Come to think of it, you look a little pale right now.
What happened? You're not sick, are you?
They said it's nothing specific.
At my age,
That's the best you can get.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I haven't been calling you.
I'll do that more often now.
Great.
Yeo-ri, I'd rather you came by more often.
Instead of waiting for me to call you over.
Yeah, that was 12 years ago.
He had a heart transplant.
But I don't see anything else other than that.
Of course. I'm telling you because I know the donor's identity is confidential.
How long will it take?
Yeah. ASAP.
PRELIMINARY BACKGROUND CHECK REPORT SUBJECT: MA GANG-UK
200 joules.
Clear.
The donor's heart has been removed, sir.
-Pil-dong? -Hmm?
Option one or option two?
-Hmm, just two? -Yeah.
-Option one. -Okay, donkkaseu.
Of course.
Violence is committed in the name of love
-Donkkaseu, cool. -we made the decision to make this letter
-available to the public -Hey. Wanna grab lunch?
-You go ahead. -Are you sure?
-We're getting donkkaseu. -Enjoy.
After we finally release it, I intend to donate it in accordance
LEE HWA-YONG, DIRECTOR OF YEEON FOUNDATION
With the last and final wishes of my late father,
First director of the Yeeon Foundation,
To my alma mater.
That's right. I heard the founding chairman
Donated just about all the old records on Kang Pyeong-gun to his old university.
Well, every investigation's gotta start somewhere, right?
And these Kang Pyeong-gun records might just lead us exactly where we need to go.
So, I'm thinking I'll swing by after work.
Oh. I was actually planning to go there.
Oh! Well, let's go together.
Okay, sure.
-Mr. Bong. -Yes?
Come a little closer.
About this afternoon's executive meeting,
Anything special on the agenda?
Uh, no, not particularly, ma'am.
Okay, well, in that case, you're going to be running the meeting yourself.
Yes.
Oh. Hey, Ms. Eom.
Do you think Ms. Cheon's been acting a little strange lately?
Yes I do, Mr. Bong. You noticed too?
Ah. I knew you'd be the right person to ask.
I guess so. She's been a little less guarded than she used to be, right?
You know what?
I feel like she's more trusting now. She's letting people in.
Especially this guy.
Ah! You saw what happened in there. She went and singled me out.
She said, "Mr. Bong, come a little closer."
And then she left the executive meeting in my hands.
It's clear as day by now.
What is clear?
Well, that she sees me as her right-hand.
Too much pressure for one person.
Do you want to know what's "too much," Mr. Bong? You are.
Ah. You're just jealous. I'm an easygoing guy.
Yeah. Yes, I'm here.
Sure, sounds great. Thanks!
He put in a word for us.
Oh, right.
Rule number two, right?
Keep a safe distance. Sorry.
The weather's amazing, isn't it?
I think my balance is off. I keep pulling to the left.
-Welcome. -Hello.
I just talked to my boss on the phone.
-He told me to help you out however I can. -We appreciate it.
-This way, Ms. Cheon. -Mm-hmm.
So many old documents in here, huh?
This is the Yeeon Foundation section.
All donated documents are here.
Is that Kang Pyeong-gun's?
This is a record of property inheritance the king issued to Lord Kang Pyeong-gun.
Kang Pyeong-gun's name is right here.
It specifies every room, even the number of kitchen bays.
It's more detailed than I thought.
Ah, is there something like
A blueprint of the house or a floor plan?
There is something along those lines. It's called a Jetaekdo.
This was Kang Pyeong-gun's residence.
Wow. Is it okay if I take a picture of this?
Wow.
This is Kang Pyeong-gun's personal anthology.
You could think of it as a collection of essays.
HWAPYEONG ANTHOLOGY
So we have these and the records about his home.
Do you have anything else here?
There's one more, his personal travel journal.
Give me a moment.
Oh! Yeo-ri, wait a minute.
Hmm?
Oh, watch out!
-What are you doing? Be careful. -Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Huh?
What's that?
Take Take a picture.
"The camellia tree by my late wife's grave."
That has to be a reference to where Hwagyeongdang was buried,
-don't you think? -Yeah, I think so too.
"I will look upon it for the rest of my days to find comfort for my heartache."
Wait a second, so that means
Hwagyeongdang's camellia tree was visible from his residence, right?
And since Yeeon now stands
On the old site of Kang Pyeong-gun's residence
Well, there you go.
There's no such thing as a perfect crime.
Even after so long,
The truth always ends up coming out.
Such a horrible obsession.
Anyway, we've got a problem.
There's no way we can check under the tree.
We can't just dig it up.
It belongs to the museum.
Yeah, I know. Ugh.
And we can't just be honest about it,
Because they'd think we're completely nuts.
Plus, this would be a disgrace to their ancestors,
So that is not an option.
We'll have to find a way to make it happen somehow.
Hwagyeongdang
Really needs to be set free.
Yeah.
Is that Cheon Yeo-ri, or am I wrong?
And who is that man?
Director Ok, hi.
Is Cheon Yeo-ri interested in the gallery, by any chance?
She's been coming here a lot lately.
Cheon Yeo-ri?
Has she been asking questions
About the hotel's artwork or anything like that?
No, nothing like that.
She's just here with some guy right now.
Oh, I see.
And the guy she's with, does it happen to be Kang Min-hwan?
No way. I'd recognize Min-hwan in a heartbeat.
And also, he'd definitely stop by to say hello.
Right.
Anyway, I'll try to drop by sometime soon to see you.
There's something I need to tell you.
Great, I hope it's good news, right?
Ah, yes.
-Mom. -Hmm?
What did Ms. Lee say?
Were Yeo-ri and Min-hwan there together?
I don't think it was him, actually. No.
Are Cheon Yeo-ri and Min-hwan actually seeing each other?
You saw the other article, right?
They're not dating yet.
Don't say "yet." Come on.
That makes it sound like they will date.
Mom, if Min-hwan and Yeo-ri get married,
That leaves us in a terrible position, doesn't it?
We'll just have to play that card again if it doesn't pan out.
You mean that thing about the ghosts?
We can't play that card, all right? We can't prove that.
People are already spreading rumors.
I heard they came from Cha Gi-u's side after the engagement ended.
-Hey, wait -Huh?
Is Cha Gi-u back in Korea?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Came back last month, I heard.
Okay.
Oh! Look! I won! Where are you going?
She's making a run for it.
So you want the real reason?
There isn't a "real" reason and a "fake" reason, is there?
I wanna know what really happened, not the PR version.
People said you went abroad to study as soon as it was called off.
I heard the rumors you've been spreading.
And the thing is, they line up with my theory, so
And what's your theory, Ms. Cheon?
I think, maybe there was something about my cousin
That was too much for you to handle, huh?
Something I couldn't handle?
-Like what, Ms. Cheon? -Well, you know
Something involving ghosts and the supernatural.
I'd like you to testify to that.
When the time comes, all right?
What happens then?
No, they were just working on the place when they found it.
Yeah.
No. No, no. You can't.
You'll end up in huge trouble if you cover up an artifact like that.
Mm-hmm. Well, first things first,
You need to report it. I'll head over there.
I'll check it out. Maybe over the weekend.
Uh-huh. I'm at work right now.
Uh-huh. Hmm.
Oh, boy.
My parents are fixing up a wall at their place,
And it turns out part of it was connected to an old fortress site or something.
-They found an artifact? -Hmm.
I heard the government pays you for that kinda stuff, right?
Do you know how much?
Yeah, well, I'm sure it's peanuts anyway. Hey--
-You're always like that. -Huh?
All All you think about is money.
Well, everyone needs money to survive, you know?
Sure. You know what else I need? Food.
-Team dinner tonight? What do you think? -Oh!
Let's have pork rind. How does that sound?
-Next time, next time. -Wait a second, hold on. Listen to me.
You are going to love this place. They actually age it right there.
-Aged pork rind. They do it right there. -Cool. Next time, next time.
You I swear to God, I'm sick of looking at his face.
I mean, you're really something else, you know that?
Did I do something to you?
Always with your sharp exits.
You're like cutting out of here like a chef with a knife.
You should do that too, actually.
You too.
See what I mean? Come on
I bet this is all because of a lady.
Right? You know who, huh?
Oh, right! Yeah. Uh-huh. Okay.
Yeah. That girl, right? That woman is probably out there.
Mm-hmm.
The only person who can turn Gang-uk
Into the king of leaving work on the dot:
His grandmother, Mrs. Pang Myo-sun.
Yeo-ri. You're here early.
Gang-uk.
Oh, I'm a little early.
But you're a little early too.
Ah. I wanted to be the first one here. I was a minute too late.
It's nice being here, huh? Makes me feel like I'm back in school.
Yeah. And it's quiet, so we won't run into anyone we know.
Ah! Listen, I came up with an idea
-so we can search under the tree. -Did you?
If you find an artifact while building on private property,
You're required to stop construction.
Cultural Heritage Law. Yup!
Oh, that's right. You would know.
In any case,
If that's our move,
I need to pull out my ace in the hole.
Hmm?
Hold on. You want to buy our camellia tree?
You mentioned it last time.
Even in the south,
Camellias with that bright magenta color are hard to find.
I want it for myself.
You know what? Honestly,
I thought you were coming here so often
Because you were interested in the business.
But this is unexpected.
Actually, some of the other things you've shown interest in
Have been a little unusual too.
-You think so? -Oh. Let me think here
Well, this camellia meant a lot to my late father.
He spent years taking care of it.
And our visitors seem to love it too.
People are always in front of it, taking pictures and all that.
I don't really see why--
I wanna keep it at home, you know?
Put it in my yard, so I can always see it.
Oh, but you can come here whenever you want.
Hmm
Wait a minute, if you don't want to sell it to me,
How about a trade instead?
Uh, for what?
Well, our family has a really rare pine tree, it's very old.
Is that so? Huh.
You and Director Ok have been really close lately, haven't you?
Well, you know, we're in the same line of work after all.
She'll know what pine tree it is.
Talk to her about it, if you want. She'll tell you.
Maybe she's already told you.
Ms. Lee, hi.
So you talked to Director Ok on the phone?
Great.
Then I'll prepare for the work on my end.
Bye.
Hmm?
Yes, hello?
I'll be right there, thank you.
Hi, Yeo-ri.
I checked with the Korea Heritage Service,
And it looks like we can proceed as planned.
That's great.
-Yeo-ri? -Yes?
Is everything okay? You seem
Sorry about that. I'm gonna have to call you back.
Good evening.
Go ahead.
You're here.
Grandma, hi.
What's going on? How are you?
Nothing, I just had a little spell, honey, that's all.
I was lucky Min-hwan was there.
He called an ambulance before anything worse happened.
No one else knows about this.
Especially not Director Ok.
Oh, Grandma
I'm not dead yet, you know?
Goodness, this isn't like you.
Hmm.
I'm so sorry.
I'll go check on Ms. Cheon.
I wonder if everything's all right.
Maybe I should go to her place?
No, too much.
I didn't want to mention this, for your sake.
But I don't really know how much time I have left.
What do you mean? What are you talking about?
You know what I was most worried about after I collapsed?
Cheon Yeo-ri.
"I can't leave her all by herself."
Cha Gi-u, your ex-fiancé.
He's been spreading rumors about why you called off the wedding.
Bury this story with a bigger one.
This is our chance to prove them all wrong.
Yeo-ri, let's put the gossip to rest.
You must announce the engagement to Min-hwan.
I'll admit it, this battle for ownership will be tough.
I know they've got plenty of support right now.
But doing that would only treat the symptoms.
That approach isn't going to fix what's really wrong.
I'll show them what I'm capable of,
And I'll win the shareholders' trust, I promise you.
The issue here is time.
I have to start the succession process right away.
You remember Director Gong and Director Jang, don't you?
They were really close with the late chairman.
They have enough shares between them
To hold the deciding vote.
As far as I remember, they've always been neutral.
Yes. And that's exactly why
We're going to approach Director Jang first.
Chairwoman Baek wants to formalize the succession
At the next shareholders' meeting.
Your mother loved Reina so much, you know?
And Siena, but that goes without saying.
If you want to protect them,
Then I'm begging you,
Listen to me this time around.
Remember last time?
The stock jumped as soon as the article dropped.
Min-hwan will have your back.
He'll be valuable to you in many ways.
You've known him since you were kids.
Gosh, Yeo-ri, why has it been so
It's been so hard to reach you. You said you'd call me later.
Is, uh Is everything okay?
My grandmother wasn't feeling well, so I went to visit her at the hospital.
Oh. I'm sorry. Is she okay?
She's all right. She's doing better now.
That's a relief.
Are you okay, Yeo-ri?
Yeah. By the way, I talked to Ms. Lee.
She accepted. We closed the deal.
We'll get it done while the museum's closed.
Okay.
So I guess we should be good to go.
-Yeah. -Yeo-ri.
Shall we have a team dinner? What do you say?
I was thinking we could have ramen by the Hangang River.
We'll see, Gang-uk.
Well, see you at the museum.
-Okay. -Bye.
YEEON MUSEUM OF ART TEMPORARY CLOSURE
Looks like we're in for some heavy rain.
Ugh. Maybe we should do it some other time.
What if Ms. Lee changes her mind out of the blue?
-Let's go ahead with it. -Okay.
Let's get started.
Okay, come on, let's begin!
-Yes, sir! -Yes, sir!
Let's start over here.
I told them to dig deep.
Once the coffin's exposed, we'll stop the work immediately and call it in.
Oh, the papers. Do we have all we need?
I filled out the report ahead of time. Everything's ready to go.
Okay.
Once we call it in, they'll send someone to check it out.
Before we know it, they'll be out here inspecting the coffin.
Director Ok, hello.
They've just started digging.
Yeah, I
Is it just me, or does something feel off?
To be honest,
It's a beautiful tree, but it's just a common camellia.
Why would she trade for such a valuable ancient tree?
Doesn't that seem a little strange to you?
Maybe she's just obsessed with that magenta color.
That's her.
Yeo-ri's always been like that.
Once her heart is set on something, she won't stop until it's hers.
Anyway, congrats on your purchase.
That's a really valuable tree, so good for you.
-Why, thank you. -Bye.
INCOMING CALL - SECRETARY WANG, CHAIRWOMAN'S OFFICE
What happens if we don't find anything?
Oh! It's raining. Come on, Yeo-ri. Come on.
-Get under the canopy! -Stop what you're doing
-Oh, it's pouring! -and get under the canopy.
Come inside, come inside!
Damn it, we barely started.
Hey, what's with the family dinner?
Are we in trouble or something?
Ha-ri, was it you? What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Well, never mind then. Why'd you get so worked up?
It's no big deal, just a family dinner, settle down.
I don't buy that. I think it's weird.
Min-hwan was invited too. Oh, no.
They're not about to get engaged, are they?
It would really suck for us if they did.
Getting engaged is no simple task.
Remember Cha Gi-u? That fell apart.
They called it off on the day of the wedding.
That's true. Cheon Yeo-ri has a way of messing things up for herself, right?
They're not getting engaged tonight.
How do you know that?
Mommy, call Director Gong for a minute.
It's not getting better. We're gonna have to call it a day.
Yes, safety first, you're right.
Let's just call it for now.
The weather's been crazy these days, right?
I know, man. It's getting crazier every year.
Grandma, hi.
A family dinner?
Min-hwan's going too?
Okay, I'll be there.
Yeo-ri, what's going on?
I
Think I'm going to have to get engaged.
Huh?
Uh, what do you mean?
Good evening.
-Oh, there you are. -Hello. Hi.
To think I'd see you here.
Happy to be here.
Great, shall we get started then?
Actually, I have something to say before we start.
Hold on a minute. Someone else will be joining us soon.
We should wait till he's here.
Just tell me this. Did you hold hands with my cousin?
I'd like you to testify to that.
When the time comes, all right?
Who is it?
We have one more guest.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Ma Gang-uk. It's a pleasure.
Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk and I
Are getting engaged.
SPOOKY IN LOVE
So it's not about business with Prosecutor Ma?
You have feelings for each other, is that true?
I like Yeo-ri a lot. We're getting engaged and I'm excited.
Tell me something, dear. What's your zodiac sign?
-What? -Your sign.
My sign?
Okay then, next.
-Back then -I was playing hard to get.
You're gonna call off the engagement, that's what you'll do.
-You're kidding me. -How about we work together?
We both want to break them up, and I know how to do it.
You remember what happened six years ago, right?
I want to know the real reason you broke off your engagement in exchange.
I think you should have a meeting.
I think Director Ok has started openly trying to keep you in check.
CIVIL SERVANT PERSONNEL RECORD MA GANG-UK
Yeo-ri can never get engaged. Not to Ma Gang-uk, or anyone else.
I've got you now, Cheon Yeo-ri.